Grant, Alice, Additional Records /4095
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Office Files (Box 11)
  - Eric Lawson - Crest, 1983-1986 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Students, 1976-1987 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Personal (Alice Grant), 1969-1987 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    Includes one color and two black and white photographs; includes news clippings
  - Steve Mongeau, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Mary Margaret Williams, 1983-1988 (Box 11, Folder 14)
- Office Files (Box 12)
  - Coordinator of Labor Programs, 1968-1982 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Educational Opportunity Center (EOC), 1979-1987 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Statewide Labor Relations, 1985-1986 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Oxford-Bureau of National Affairs (BNA) Symposium, 1982-1988 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Annual Reports, 1980-1988 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Annual Reports (before 1980), 1964-1980 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Extension Committee, 1982-1986 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Peer Review - Susan Woods, 1986-1987 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Peer Review - Lou Jean Fleron, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Search Committee, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    The original dates on the documents are from 1981, but these are crossed out and replaced with 1984
  - Michele Kaplan, 1981-1987 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Mona Miller, 1981-1987 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Statewide Labor Relations 1986-1987 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Wallen Fund, 1969-1988 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Office Files (Box 13)
  - Arbitration, 1971-1985 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Arbitrator Development - Wingspread Conference 1977, 1964-1977 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    June 9-10, 1977; includes a brochure for the Wingspread building
  - Arbitrator Development Program - Administrator, 1972-1987 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Arbitrator Training, 1972-1988 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Arbitration Training Materials, 1961-1982 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Hanover Tenants Union, Rochester, 1965-1968 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Cathy Nichols Questionnaire - International Union of Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers (IUE), 1969 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - IUE, Rochester, 1971-1978 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - IUE Education Opportunity Program - Western New York, 1969-1972 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Politics - Reform Democrats, 1953-1954 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    Includes many news clippings; includes a vinyl record
  - William A. Nowlin, 1985-1988 (Box 13, Folder 11)